[{"answer": "Piers, a senior U.S. official just saying those very words to me.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "What can you tell me about it?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "It certainly is worrying, very provocative according to administration officials here.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "It's an escalation?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't want to be the head of North Korea's space agency right now.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "I mean, clearly, we knew it was happening, it's been a failure, but what is the bigger, wider significance?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Let me just hold you, Governor.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Ignore United Nations, carry on like dad used to do.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Didn't go very well, did it?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "You know, there is a lot out there that says it has come from -- there has been Iranian involvement over the year, and it's very interesting that you ask that, because senior U.S. officials will tell you that they believe the sanctions against North Korea have kept the really precision equipment out of there.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "And is it right that some of that equipment's come from Iran in this particular case?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Well, the clever way, I thought the White House statement was prudent and clever.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "How -- what is the clever way of responding to this potentially very unstable situation?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Mr. Zimmerman, you're appearing here for your first appearances -- first appearance at this time for charge of murder in the second degree and you are represented by Mr. O'Mara, is that true?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Well, a couple of goals.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "But what is your goal?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Well, he's afraid and he's stressed and he's tired.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "What were your first impressions of George Zimmerman as a man?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "'MARA: I was not aware of that until that was reported in the news.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "He is very concerned about the way he has been portrayed and the way that this case has sort of seemingly gotten almost out of control, starting with maybe the way it was handled early on in the investigation by law enforcement.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "How does he feel?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "You know, I've not talked to him about the facts of the case.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Do you believe that he regrets getting out of the car and following Trayvon Martin at all?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, you know, there's a split system here.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Do you believe that he, if he had the chance to do so, would make such an apology?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Without having seen the evidence, my presumption is that they've kept the probable cause affidavit as thin as they thought they could, to maybe limit the amount of information in there that's flowing out.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "First of all, I'm thrilled that there is a good lawyer involved in this case.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, I think that probable cause affidavit is really a lot to do about nothing.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What do you think of what's gone on today?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "This is ant game of poker.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "But do you believe, like a good Poker player, and as Mr. O'Mara suggested to me, that she has got a few cards up her sleeve, and just isn't showing them yet?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I was a part, along with Mr. Dershowitz, of the O.J. Simpson defense team.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "When you introduce fame, notoriety, public opinion, the media and so on, what difference does that make?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, the major contraction, I think, was in the first interview, he basically said that Martin confronted him and spoke to him and said, \"why are you following me?\"", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What did you think of it?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's a very difficult question for me to answer.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Do you think that the Stand Your Ground law is fundamentally flawed?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "If you were prosecuting this case against George Zimmerman right now, would you be confident of a conviction of second- degree murder, from everything we're currently aware of?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, quite honestly, I think about my mom and the work that she did do.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Josh, when you heard that your mother had never done a day's work in her life, what was your honest reaction?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Reality is we never had anyone in the house.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What was the reality?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "You know, you hear a lot of things in the campaign trail.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Did you feel quite hurt on her behalf at this slur?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "You guys must be quietly rubbing your hands in glee, aren't you?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I hope at -- you know, I hope that at the White House they actually have washing machines.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Are we going to have a president potentially who, every week, goes to a sink and hand washes his shirts?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Piers, I wish I had an hour glass.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Stan, what can you tell me about what's happening there?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "It certainly is very embarrassing and potentially I guess pretty dangerous for the world.", "docId": "120412pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 569}]